A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1985-1986
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1985-1986
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.881
This collection consists of 500 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1987 July 10.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: administrative committee files.
Contents List
- Series I: Administrative Committees Files, 1985-1986
  - General 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Admissions 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Afro-American Affairs Advisory 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Algernon Sydney Sullivan Award 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Arboretum and Landscape 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Architectural Advisory (empty) 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Athletic Advisory Council 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Bayly Museum 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Calendar 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Cemetery 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Chapel 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Chemical and Biological Hazards Safety 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Chemical and Biological Hazards Safety--Subcommittee--DNA 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Commencement and Convocations 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Commencement and Convocations--Subcommittee--Processions 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Commencement and Convocations--Subcommittee--Public Occasions 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Community Colleges 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Computers (empty) 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Education and Employment--Opportunity, Obligations, and Rights 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Energy Conservation 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Fraternities and Sororities 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Fulbright Grants 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Graphics 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Gwathmey Award 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Housing 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - International Students 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Lectures--Page, Barbours, and Richard 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Library 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - Library--Subcommittee--Science and Engineering Library 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Master Plan (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Names 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Proxy Advisory 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Radiation Safety 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Radiation Safety--Subcommittee--Radioactive Drug Research 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Registration 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Residential Life 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Rhodes Scholarships 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - ROTC 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Scheduling 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Scholarships, Grant-in-Aid, Employment, and Loans 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Security and General Safety 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Student Activities 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Student Health 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Summer Grants 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Summer Sessions 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Traffic Appeals 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Traffic and Parking 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Truman Scholarship 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - University Committee on Students 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - University Press 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - University Union and Student Activities Building 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1985-1986 (Box 2)
  - Virginia Status of University Students 1985-1986 (Box 2)